v1.2.22
1 fix a bug of contract testing
2 fix a bug when registering token contract


v1.2.21
1 fix a bug of contract
2 add a safe_random interface of contract
3 legacy address of BCH is now compatible
4 modify the display of exchange bill depth

All users must upgrade to this version.


v1.2.20
1 add new coin BCH
2 optimize the memory usage
3 the K-line widget is displayed on a side-by-side interface.
4 show the block height of network at the bottom

If you upgrade to this version, your wallet will replay the chain data. This will take you a few minutes.


v1.2.19
1 fix a bug of creating multi-sig addresses
2 fix a display bug when senators update keys


v1.2.18
1 fix a bug of withdrawing ELF
2 fix a bug of multi-sig account
3 optimize performance
4 optimize the communication with middleware
5 fix a bug witch may destroy the DB
6 now users can cancel the withdraw of HIOU when the trx is in pending state
7 k-line graph is added in the exchange page


v1.2.16
1 optimize the synchronization
2 change the action when contract storage change from table to nil

in case that the network connection num is still 0 or the block height is not increasing, please remove dir "blockchain" in chaindata path and restart hx-indicator

v1.2.15
1 fix a crash bug


v1.2.14
1 network optimized
2 change contract storage format
3 decentralized exchange released
4 open special deposit channel


v1.2.12
1 add a new coin USDT
2 fix a crash bug
3 fix some other bugs


v1.2.11
1 optimize node performance
2 lock position contract
3 fix some other bugs


v1.2.10
1 fix a bug of fee acceptance
2 fix a bug when new user login first time
3 fix a bug of ETH crosschain withdraw block
4 fix some other bugs


v1.2.9
1 fix a deposit bug


v1.2.8
1 fix a crash bug

v1.2.7
1 fix ELF transfer bug

v1.2.6
1 add new ERC20 token ELF
2 add checkpoint function
3 fix querytrans bug
4 optimize "importAddr"
5 fix some other bugs


v1.2.5
1 improve node performance
2 optimize rpc priority
3 fix some other bugs


v1.2.4
1 optimize the interface of contract
2 generate .dmp file when the wallet crashed on windows
3 fix a bug of ETH withdrawal
4 page of contract token will be displayed faster
5 fix some other bugs


v1.2.3
1. optimize Interaction with Middleware
2. increase shutdown and startup speed
3. support batch operation when pledge and foreclose
4. fix some other bugs



v1.2.1
1. now wallet will be launched faster
2. reduce the frequency of accessing Middleware
3. optimizing bonus distribution strategy
4. now you can add some favorite pairs in order center
5. now you can select the appropriate gas price when you allot ETH or ERC assets
6. fix some bugs


v1.2.0
1. fix withdrawal status change bug


v1.1.9
1. add new coin ERC20-PAX
2. fix some bugs
